Office of Corporate and Foundation Relations Records UA199
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Foundation Prospect Files, 1959 -- 2008; 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002; 19.2 Linear Feet
  - Mailman Foundation, 1991 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Markay Charitable Trust, Lucille P [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1998; UA199.002.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Markay Charitable Trust, Lucille P [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1998; UA199.002.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Markle Foundation, 1989 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00005 (Box 22)
  - Mars Foundation, 1990 -- 1991; UA199.002.022.00006 (Box 22)
  - Massachusetts Children's Trust, 2006; UA199.002.022.00007 (Box 22)
  - Massachusetts Foundation for Humanities, 1999; UA199.002.022.00008 (Box 22)
  - Matsushita Foundation, 1986 -- 1990; UA199.002.022.00009 (Box 22)
  - McDonald Foundation, J. M. [1 of 3], 1985 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00010 (Box 22)
  - McDonnell Foundation, James S. [1 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00011 (Box 22)
  - McDonnell Foundation, James S. [2 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00012 (Box 22)
  - McDonnell Foundation, James S. [3 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00013 (Box 22)
  - McKnight Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.022.00014 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.022.00015 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.022.00016 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W, 2000 -- 2002; UA199.002.022.00017 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. [1 of 2], 1998 -- 2000; UA199.002.022.00018 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. [2 of 2], 1998 -- 2000; UA199.002.022.00019 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. [1 of 3], 1984 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00020 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. [2 of 3], 1984 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00021 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Andrew W. [3 of 3], 1984 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00022 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Richard King [1 of 3], 1980 -- 1989; UA199.002.022.00023 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Richard King [2 of 3], 1980 -- 1989; UA199.002.022.00024 (Box 22)
  - Mellon Foundation, Richard King [3 of 3], 1980 -- 1989; UA199.002.022.00025 (Box 22)
  - Merck Family Fund, 1992 -- 1995; UA199.002.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1982 -- 2002; UA199.002.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Micronutrient Initiative, 1999; UA199.002.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Milken Family Medical Foundation, 1990 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Millbank Foundation, 1981; UA199.002.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Millbank Memorial Fund, 1979 -- 1988; UA199.002.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Milwaukee Foundation, 2000; UA199.002.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Minneapolis Foundation, 1998; UA199.002.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Moore Foundation, Gordon and Betty, 2002; UA199.002.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - Moriah Fund, 1994 -- 2001; UA199.002.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - Morris Animal Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - Morse Foundation, Martha, 2001; UA199.002.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - Ruth Mott Foundation, 1983 -- 1997; UA199.002.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - Mott, Stewart R. [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1991; UA199.002.022.00039 (Box 22)
  - Mott, Stewart R. [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1991; UA199.002.022.00040 (Box 22)
  - Mott Foundation, Charles Stewart [1 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Mott Foundation, Charles Stewart [2 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Mott Foundation, Charles Stewart [1 of 2], 1992 -- 1999; UA199.002.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Mott Foundation, Charles Stewart [2 of 2], 1992 -- 1999; UA199.002.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Mott Foundation, Charles Stewart, 1977 -- 1991; UA199.002.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - "N" Misc., 2004 -- 2008; UA199.002.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Nakamichi Foundation, 1995; UA199.002.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1983; UA199.002.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - National Fund for Medical Education, 1994; UA199.002.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - National Osteoporosis Business Coalition, 1999 -- 2001; UA199.002.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - National Science Foundation, 1987 -- 1994; UA199.002.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 2000; UA199.002.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - New American Schools Development Corporation (NASDC), 1991; UA199.002.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - New England College Fund, 1999; UA199.002.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - New England Foundation for the Arts, 1987; UA199.002.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - New World Foundation, 1982 -- 1987; UA199.002.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Newhouse Foundation, 1985 -- 1999; UA199.002.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - New Profit, Inc., 1999; UA199.002.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Nike, 1997 -- 1998; UA199.002.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Noble Foundation, Edward John, 1981 -- 1985; UA199.002.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - North American Commission for Environmental Cooperation, 2001 -- 2002; UA199.002.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Noyes Memorial Foundation, Nicholas H., 2000; UA199.002.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Noyes Foundation, Jessie Smith [1 of 2], 1984 -- 1999; UA199.002.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Noyes Foundation, Jessie Smith [2 of 2], 1977 -- 1983; UA199.002.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - "O" Misc., 2005 -- 2007; UA199.002.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Oak Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Old Colony Charitable Foundation, 1982 -- 1998; UA199.002.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Olin Foundation, John M., 1980 -- 1999; UA199.002.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Olin Foundation, F. W. [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1996; UA199.002.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Olin Foundation, F. W. [2 of 2], 1988 -- 1991; UA199.002.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Olin Foundation, Spencer T. and Ann W., 1998 -- 2002; UA199.002.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Onassis Foundation, 1983 -- 1984; UA199.002.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Open Society Institute, 2000; UA199.002.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - "P" Misc., 2007 -- 2008; UA199.002.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Packard Foundation, David and Lucille [1 of 2], 2001 -- 2004; UA199.002.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Packard Foundation, David and Lucille [2 of 2], 1998 -- 2000; UA199.002.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - Packard Foundation, David and Lucille [1 of 2], 1983 -- 1997; UA199.002.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - Packard Foundation, David and Lucille [2 of 2], 1979 -- 1983; UA199.002.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - Pappas Charitable Trust, Thomas A., 1983 -- 1994; UA199.002.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Parker Foundation, Theodore Edson, 1999; UA199.002.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Amelia Peabody Foundation, 1977 -- 1997; UA199.002.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Pediatric AIDS Foundation, 1995 -- 1997; UA199.002.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Perkin Fund, 2001; UA199.002.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Petroleum Research (1988-present) [1 of 5], 1993 -- 1998; UA199.002.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Petroleum Research (1988-present) [2 of 5], 1991 -- 1992; UA199.002.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Petroleum Research (1988-present) [3 of 5], 1989 -- 1991; UA199.002.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Petroleum Research (1988-present) [4 of 5], 1988 -- 1990; UA199.002.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Petroleum Research (1988-present) [5 of 5], 1988 -- 1989; UA199.002.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Pew Conservation (1990-present) [1 of 2], 1990 -- 1999; UA199.002.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Pew Conservation (1990-present) [2 of 2], UA199.002.024.00012 (Box 24)
  - Pew Education A&S #1 [1 of 2], 1993 -- 2001; UA199.002.024.00013 (Box 24)
  - Pew Education A&S #1 [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1993; UA199.002.024.00014 (Box 24)
  - Pew Education A&S #2 [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1989; UA199.002.024.00015 (Box 24)
  - Pew Education A&S #2 [2 of 2], 1985 -- 1990; UA199.002.024.00016 (Box 24)
  - Pew Health Sciences (Dental) [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA199.002.024.00017 (Box 24)
  - Pew Health Sciences (Dental) [2 of 2], 1987; UA199.002.024.00018 (Box 24)
  - Pew Fletcher, 1986 -- 1997; UA199.002.024.00019 (Box 24)
  - Pew Trusts (General) [1 of 3], 1986 -- 2000; UA199.002.024.00020 (Box 24)
  - Pew Trusts (General) [2 of 3], 1996 -- 1997; UA199.002.024.00021 (Box 24)
  - Pew Trusts (General) [3 of 3], 1987 -- 2006; UA199.002.024.00022 (Box 24)
  - Pew Medical (1990-present) [1 of 3], 1995 -- 2000; UA199.002.024.00023 (Box 24)
  - Pew Medical (1990-present) [2 of 3], 1994; UA199.002.024.00024 (Box 24)
  - Pew Medical (1990-present) [3 of 3], 1990 -- 1993; UA199.002.024.00025 (Box 24)
  - Pew Health Sciences (Nutrition), 1985 -- 2001; UA199.002.024.00026 (Box 24)
  - Pew Foundation, UCCPS, 1992; UA199.002.024.00027 (Box 24)
  - PEW-Health Science (Veterinary) [1 of 2], 1993 -- 2002; UA199.002.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - PEW-Health Science (Veterinary) [2 of 2], 1991 -- 1993; UA199.002.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [1 of 2], 2000 -- 2002; UA199.002.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [2 of 2], 2000; UA199.002.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [1 of 2], 2002 -- 2003; UA199.002.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [2 of 2], 2001; UA199.002.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [1 of 2], 1997 -- 1998; UA199.002.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Pfeiffer Foundation, George [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1997; UA199.002.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Philanthropic Institute, 2000; UA199.002.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Pierce Charitable Foundation, Harold Whitworth, 1979 -- 1998; UA199.002.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Planck Institute, Max, 1999 -- 2004; UA199.002.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - Ploughshares Fund, 1982 -- 1995; UA199.002.025.00012 (Box 25)
  - Prince Charitable Trust, 1979 -- 1980; UA199.002.025.00013 (Box 25)
  - Prince of Wales Foundation, 2000; UA199.002.025.00014 (Box 25)
  - Fritzker Foundation, Jay, 2002; UA199.002.025.00015 (Box 25)
  - Public Welfare Foundation [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1998; UA199.002.025.00016 (Box 25)
  - Public Welfare Foundation [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1990; UA199.002.025.00017 (Box 25)
  - "R" Misc., 2003 -- 2007; UA199.002.025.00018 (Box 25)
  - Ratshesky Foundation, A. C., 1982 -- 1998; UA199.002.025.00019 (Box 25)
  - Reed, Joseph V. Ambassador, 2000; UA199.002.025.00020 (Box 25)
  - Resources for the Future, 1982 -- 1994; UA199.002.025.00021 (Box 25)
  - Retirement Research Foundation #1 [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1994; UA199.002.025.00022 (Box 25)
  - Retirement Research Foundation #1 [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1994; UA199.002.025.00023 (Box 25)
  - Retirement Research Foundation #2 [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1994; UA199.002.025.00024 (Box 25)
  - Retirement Research Foundation #2 [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1994; UA199.002.025.00025 (Box 25)
  - Revson Foundation, Charles H, 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - Ripples Foundation, Fannie [1 of 3], 1983 -- 1996; UA199.002.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - Ripples Foundation, Fannie [2 of 3], 1983 -- 1996; UA199.002.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - Ripple Foundation, Fannie [3 of 3], 1983 -- 1996; UA199.002.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Brothers [1 of 3], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Brothers [2 of 3], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Brothers [3 of 3], 1988 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [1 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [2 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [3 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [4 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00011 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [5 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00012 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [6 of 6], 2000 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00013 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [1 of 3], 1986 -- 1993; UA199.002.026.00014 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [2 of 3], 1986 -- 1993; UA199.002.026.00015 (Box 26)
  - Rockefeller Foundation [3 of 3], 1986 -- 1993; UA199.002.026.00016 (Box 26)
  - Rubin Foundation, Samuel, 1982 -- 2003; UA199.002.026.00017 (Box 26)
  - Rubin Foundation, Shelley and Donald, 1995; UA199.002.026.00018 (Box 26)
  - Rubinstein Foundation, 1995; UA199.002.026.00019 (Box 26)
  - "S" misc, 1996 -- 2004; UA199.002.026.00020 (Box 26)
  - SBC Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.026.00021 (Box 26)
  - San Antonio Area Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.026.00022 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Scholl Foundation [1 of 4], 1980 -- 1995; UA199.002.026.00023 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Scholl Foundation [2 of 4], 1980 -- 1995; UA199.002.026.00024 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Scholl Foundation [3 of 4], 1980 -- 1995; UA199.002.026.00025 (Box 26)
  - Dr. Scholl Foundation [4 of 4], 1980 -- 1995; UA199.002.026.00026 (Box 26)
  - Schlumberger Foundation, 1980 -- 2000; UA199.002.026.00027 (Box 26)
  - Schrafft Charitable Trust, William and Bertha, 2000 -- 2001; UA199.002.026.00028 (Box 26)
  - Schumann Foundation, 1990 -- 1998; UA199.002.026.00029 (Box 26)
  - Schwartz Center, The Kenneth, 2002; UA199.002.026.00030 (Box 26)
  - Seraph Foundation, 1997 -- 2002; UA199.002.026.00031 (Box 26)
  - Shader Family Fund, 1999; UA199.002.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - Search Institute, 2003; UA199.002.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - SOS Foundation (Share Our Strength), 1995 -- 2001; UA199.002.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - Simpson Charitable Trust, Marilyn, 2002 -- 2004; UA199.002.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. [1 of 2], 1990 -- 2003; UA199.002.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - Sloan Foundation, Alfred P. [2 of 2], 1992; UA199.002.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - Sloan Foundation, Alfred P., 1990 -- 1991; UA199.002.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - Smith Foundation, Richard and Susan, 1994 -- 2002; UA199.002.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - Smith Foundation, Richard and Susan [1 of 2], 1991 -- 1994; UA199.002.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - Smith Foundation, Richard and Susan [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1992; UA199.002.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - Soros Foundation, Paul and Daisy, 2001 -- 2002; UA199.002.027.00011 (Box 27)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1999 -- 2000; UA199.002.027.00012 (Box 27)
  - Spencer Foundation, 1988 -- 1998; UA199.002.027.00013 (Box 27)
  - Spunk Fund, Inc., 1996 -- 1999; UA199.002.027.00014 (Box 27)
  - Stearns Charitable Foundation, Anna B., 1992 -- 1996; UA199.002.027.00015 (Box 27)
  - Stoddard Charitable Trust, 1982 -- 1997; UA199.002.027.00016 (Box 27)
  - Stratford Foundation Inc. [1 of 2], 1993 -- 2001; UA199.002.027.00017 (Box 27)
  - Stratford Foundation Inc. [2 of 2], 1990 -- 1992; UA199.002.027.00018 (Box 27)
  - Strauss Canada Foundation, Richard and Edith, 1998; UA199.002.027.00019 (Box 27)
  - Sudbury Foundation, 2004; UA199.002.027.00020 (Box 27)
  - "T" Misc., 2005 -- 2007; UA199.002.027.00021 (Box 27)
  - Thrasher Foundation [1 of 2], 1988 -- 1997; UA199.002.027.00022 (Box 27)
  - Thrasher Foundation [2 of 2], 1980 -- 1984; UA199.002.027.00023 (Box 27)
  - Tides Center, 2002; UA199.002.027.00024 (Box 27)
  - Travelli, 1978 -- 1989; UA199.002.027.00025 (Box 27)
  - Trefler Foundation, 1999; UA199.002.027.00026 (Box 27)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding, 1990 -- 2003; UA199.002.027.00027 (Box 27)
  - Turner Foundation, 1991 -- 1995; UA199.002.027.00028 (Box 27)
  - "U" Misc., 2007; UA199.002.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - United Nations Foundation, 1998 -- 2002; UA199.002.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - US-Israel Bi-national Science Foundation, 2002 -- 2007; UA199.002.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - United States-Japan Foundation (Sasakawa), 1981 -- 2005; UA199.002.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - US Potato Board, 2003 -- 2004; UA199.002.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - "V" Misc., 2007; UA199.002.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - Van Andel Institute, 1996; UA199.002.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - Van Ameringen Foundation, Inc., 1985 -- 1989; UA199.002.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - Vanguard Charitable Endowment Program, 2003 -- 2004; UA199.002.028.00009 (Box 28)
  - Verney Foundation, 2001; UA199.002.028.00010 (Box 28)
  - Vetlesse Foundation, G. Unger, 2001; UA199.002.028.00011 (Box 28)
  - Villers Foundation, 1983 -- 1986; UA199.002.028.00012 (Box 28)
  - "W" Misc., 2004 -- 2007; UA199.002.028.00013 (Box 28)
  - Waitt Family Foundation, 2003 -- 2004; UA199.002.028.00014 (Box 28)
  - Wallace Genetic Foundation, 1987 -- 2003; UA199.002.028.00015 (Box 28)
  - Wallace Fund, Lila, 1991 -- 1993; UA199.002.028.00016 (Box 28)
  - Wallace Foundation, Dewitt, 1999; UA199.002.028.00017 (Box 28)
  - Washington Campus, 1995 -- 2001; UA199.002.028.00018 (Box 28)
  - Webster Foundation, Edwin S., 1979 -- 1988; UA199.002.028.00019 (Box 28)
  - Wellesley College, 1999; UA199.002.028.00020 (Box 28)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation, 1983 -- 1994; UA199.002.028.00021 (Box 28)
  - Wetterberg Foundation, Harold, 1978 -- 2001; UA199.002.028.00022 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation, 1990 -- 1995; UA199.002.028.00023 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation, 1987 -- 1989; UA199.002.028.00024 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation [1 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.028.00025 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation [2 of 2], 1999 -- 2002; UA199.002.028.00026 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation [1 of 2], 1996 -- 1998; UA199.002.028.00027 (Box 28)
  - Whitaker Foundation [2 of 2], 1996 -- 1998; UA199.002.028.00028 (Box 28)
  - Whitehall [1 of 2], 1977 -- 1996; UA199.002.028.00029 (Box 28)
  - Whitehall [2 of 2], 1978 -- 1980; UA199.002.028.00030 (Box 28)
  - Whiting Foundation, 1977 -- 2002; UA199.002.028.00031 (Box 28)
  - Wingwalker Initiatives Foundation, 2002; UA199.002.028.00032 (Box 28)
  - Winston Institute for Peace, 1994 -- 1998; UA199.002.028.00033 (Box 28)
  - Witherby Foundation, 2001 -- 2005; UA199.002.028.00034 (Box 28)
  - Wolfson Foundation, 1980 -- 1985; UA199.002.028.00035 (Box 28)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship (PGM), 1996; UA199.002.028.00036 (Box 28)
  - World Health Organization, 2001; UA199.002.028.00037 (Box 28)